{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Chimney Cap Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/62310/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62310,"taskName":"Chimney Cap - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Chimney Cap","xmTaskDescriptor":"Chimney Cap Services","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"chimney cap fireplace","textMessagingName":"Install Chimney Cap","rolloverLongDesc":"Replace damaged or install a new chimney cap or chimney cover.","rolloverShortDesc":"Chimney cap installation or replacement","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Chimney Cap.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Chimney Cap Installation Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Chimney Cap Replacement","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Chimney Cap Installation","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Chimney Cap - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Chimney Cap Project","urlName":"Chimney-Cap-Install-and-Replace","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Chimney Cap Installation Services in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"chimney, cap, fireplace","emcCategoryOid":-12014,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8756,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62310/":{"taskOID":62310,"originalTaskOID":62310,"setID":8756,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":502973,"questionDisplayText":"Do you already have a chimney cap?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you already have a chimney cap?","shortQuestionText":"Do you already have a chimney cap?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502974,"questionDisplayText":"How many chimney caps do you need installed?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many chimney caps do you need installed?","shortQuestionText":"How many chimney caps do you need installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502975,"questionDisplayText":"What type of chimney cap do you want installed?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of chimney cap do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of chimney cap do you want installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6036,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard","answerDisplayText":"Standard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203895,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Draft Increasing","answerDisplayText":"Draft Increasing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203896,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Integral Damper Mechanism","answerDisplayText":"Integral Damper Mechanism","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203897,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Single Flue","answerDisplayText":"Single Flue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203898,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Band-Around Brick","answerDisplayText":"Band-Around Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203899,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Top Mount","answerDisplayText":"Top Mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1747,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Custom","answerDisplayText":"Custom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":502973,"questionDisplayText":"Do you already have a chimney cap?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you already have a chimney cap?","shortQuestionText":"Do you already have a chimney cap?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502974,"questionDisplayText":"How many chimney caps do you need installed?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many chimney caps do you need installed?","shortQuestionText":"How many chimney caps do you need installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502975,"questionDisplayText":"What type of chimney cap do you want installed?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of chimney cap do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of chimney cap do you want installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6036,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard","answerDisplayText":"Standard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203895,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Draft Increasing","answerDisplayText":"Draft Increasing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203896,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Integral Damper Mechanism","answerDisplayText":"Integral Damper Mechanism","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203897,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Single Flue","answerDisplayText":"Single Flue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203898,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Band-Around Brick","answerDisplayText":"Band-Around Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203899,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Top Mount","answerDisplayText":"Top Mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1747,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Custom","answerDisplayText":"Custom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6036,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard","answerDisplayText":"Standard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203895,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Draft Increasing","answerDisplayText":"Draft Increasing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203896,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Integral Damper Mechanism","answerDisplayText":"Integral Damper Mechanism","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203897,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Single Flue","answerDisplayText":"Single Flue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203898,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Band-Around Brick","answerDisplayText":"Band-Around Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203899,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Top Mount","answerDisplayText":"Top Mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1747,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Custom","answerDisplayText":"Custom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}